

CONTACT

www.pablonudel.com

pablonudel@gmail.com

(I) +33 6 70 64 48 25

Toulouse, France

in pablonudel

pablonudel

LANGUAGES

Spanish French English

SOFTWARE

Visual Studio Code Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe AfterEffects Adobe XD Blender Wordpress

SKILS

Html 5
Css 3 & Sass
Tailwind
Bootstrap
Javascript
ReactJS
ThreeJS
NextJS
NodeJS
ExpressJS
MongoDB

SQL

Git

PABLO NUDEL

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

I have extensive experience in various creative disciplines, including Art Direction, Illustration, Motion Graphics, 2D Animation, Graphic Design, and Web Design, as well as in client management and overall project direction. I am currently focused on front-end development while continuing to expand my knowledge in this field.

EXPERIENCE

2007 - 03/2022

03/2022 - 06/2023

Web Builder & Design Project Associate

@ Luxury Presence - www.luxurypresence.com

As a web builder, I created websites for luxury real estate agents and brokerages. This included implementing, configuring, and optimizing custom assets and components. As a Design Project Associate, I performed QA, CSS improvements, tracking, feedback, and approvals in the stages leading up to site launch.

Freelance Art Direction, Illustration, Motion Graphics

& Graphic Design

Over several years, I managed and developed comprehensive projects for personal clients to which I've contributed my expertise in various design and visual arts domains. As a consultant, I have joined various teams within numerous audiovisual production studios, including: Turner International Argentina, Gazz, StoryStudio, Mandinga, Candela Creative Group and Gato.

Clients: MTV. Coca-Cola, TCM Channel, Citi Bank, Personal.

09/2004 - 04/2007

Project Manager of Multimedia Department

@ IMC Comunicación

I carried out various multimedia projects, landing pages, microsites and product presentations. I collaborated in project management and team coordination.

Clients: Microsoft, Nokia, Pirelli, PwC.

06/2002 - 03/2004

Graphic Design

@ GR Group - www.grgroup.com.ar

Branding, Corporate identity, Editorial Design, Multimedia Design.

ACADEMIC EDUCATION

2001 - 2007

Graphic Design

@ Universidad de Buenos Aires Not finished (90% complete)

COURSES & CERTIFICATIONS

09/2021 - 11/2022

Full Stack Development

@ Coderhouse - www.coderhouse.com

HTML, CSS, Git, GitHub, Boostrap, Sass, SEO, Javascript, React, Node.Js, Express, API RESTFul, Websockets, MongoDB, SQL,

Testing, GraphQL